- Maybe we should get you home.
- Hang on, hang on, hang on. Sheldon...
(Amy:)...what would it take
for you to go into that Iiquor store...
(Amy:)...buy a bottle of hooch, take me
across the street to that motel...
(Amy:)...and have your way with me?
(Leonard:)Yeah, Sheldon, what would it take?
(Sheldon:)I'm begging both of you,
please, let's go.
(Leonard:)Okay. Come on. Upsy-daisy.
Whee. Ooh!
Finally, someone found second base.
(Amy:)I know how you feel.
(Amy:)I got a knife
slicing through my frontal lobe too.
(Sheldon:)Hi.
(Amy:)What do you want?
(Amy:)Do you want me
to give the friendship bracelet back?
(Penny:)I never gave you a friendship bracelet.
When we met, I made one
and pretended you gave it to me.
(Amy:)You can have it back if you want.